<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoNFine</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="assesment_btn">Self-Assessment Test</string>
    <string name="warning">The information from this self assessment will be used to monitor your current health status so try to choose most accurate answer. The information will be also used for monitoring and management of current health crisis and research in our fight against corona</string>
    <string name="understand">OK, I Understand</string>
    <string name="gender_select">Choose your Gender</string>
    <string name="cough">Cough</string>
    <string name="muffled">Muffled/Change in Voice</string>
    <string name="breath">Shortness of Breath</string>
    <string name="fever">Fever</string>
    <string name="nausea">Nausea</string>
    <string name="diarrhoea">Diarrhoea</string>
    <string name="sense">Loss of sense of Smell/Taste</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="diabetes">Diabetes</string>
    <string name="hyper">Hypertension</string>
    <string name="lungs">Any kind of Lung Disease</string>
    <string name="heart">Any kind of Heart Disease</string>
    <string name="kidney">Kidney Disorders</string>
    <string name="blood">Blood Disorders</string>
    <string name="immune">Immunodeficiency</string>
    <string name="contact1">"I have recently come in  contact/ lived with a person tested positive for corona "</string>
    <string name="contact2">I am a health worker and have  examined a COVID positive  patient without protective gear</string>
    <string name="less_5">Less than 5 days</string>
    <string name="more_5">More than 5 days</string>
    <string name="more_14">More tha 14 days</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="pregnant">Are you Expecting a child?</string>
    <string name="smoke">Do you Smoke?</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Do you have any of the following Symptoms?</string>
    <string name="travel">Have you travelled in the last 28–45 days?</string>
    <string name="contact_days">Please specify, you have come in contact in</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="skip">If None, Click Next</string>
    <string name="liver">Liver Disorder</string>
    <string name="age">Tell us about your age</string>
    <string name="more10">10–39</string>
    <string name="more40">40–79</string>
    <string name="more80"><![CDATA[>80]]></string>
    <string name="self_assesment_test">SELF-ASSESSMENT TEST</string>
    <string name="result">RESULT</string>
    <string name="warning_result"><![CDATA[*This is based on your current health status and  the options selected by you during questionnaire  Please do consult the doctor & take their  advice in case you don’t feel good.]]></string>
    <string name="excersise_plan">Exercise Plan</string>
    <string name="diet_plan">Diet Plan</string>
    <string name="no_risk">NO RISK</string>
    <string name="no_risk_desc">No Worries my Friend!</string>
    <string name="very_low_srisk">VERY LOW RISK</string>
    <string name="very_low_risk_desc">Just follow our Diet and Exercise plans!</string>
    <string name="low_risk">LOW RISK</string>
    <string name="mild_risk">MILD RISK</string>
    <string name="moderate_risk">MODERATE RISK</string>
    <string name="significant_risk">SIGNIFICANT RISK</string>
    <string name="significant_risk_desc">We recommend you to see a  doctor!</string>
    <string name="major_risk">MAJOR RISK</string>
    <string name="high_risk">HIGH RISK</string>
    <string name="serious_risk">SERIOUS RISK</string>
    <string name="extrme_risk">EXTREME RISK</string>
    <string name="contact_people">"Which of the following apply  to you? "</string>
    <string name="caretaker_1">How do I take care of someone who\'s quarantined in my home?</string>
    <string name="caretaker_2">✔\t Help the person who is sick follow their doctor’s instructions for care and medicine.For most people, symptoms last a few days, and people usually feel better after a week.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_3">✔\t See if over-the-counter medicines for fever help the person feel better.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_4">✔\t Make sure the person who is sick drinks a lot of fluids and rests.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_5">✔\t Help them with grocery shopping, filling prescriptions, and getting other items they may need. Consider having the items delivered through a delivery service, if possible.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_6">✔\t Take care of their pet(s), and limit contact between the person who is sick and their pet(s) when possible.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_7">✔\t Call their doctor if the person keeps getting sicker. Limit contact with the patient and do not share personal items.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_8">✔\t tClean your hands regularly.</string>
    <string name="caretaker_9">WHEN TO SEEK FOR MEDICAL HELP?</string>
    <string name="caretaker_10">If someone is showing any of these signs, seek emergency medical care immediately:</string>
    <string name="caretaker_11">✔\t Trouble breathing</string>
    <string name="caretaker_12">✔\t Persistent pain or pressure in the chest</string>
    <string name="caretaker_13">✔\t New confusion</string>
    <string name="caretaker_14">✔\t Inability to wake or stay awake</string>
    <string name="caretaker_15">✔\t Bluish lips or face</string>
    <string name="caretaker_16">⭐\t This list is not all the possible symptoms. Please call your medical provider for any other symptoms that are severe or concerning to you.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_12">✔\t Patients with confirmed COVID-19 should remain under home isolation precautions until the risk of secondary transmission to others is thought to be low. The decision to discontinue home isolation precautions is made on a case-by-case basis, in consultation with health care providers, and state and local health departments.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_11">"✔\t People who are placed under active monitoring or facilitated self-monitoring should follow instructions provided by their local health department or occupational health professionals, as appropriate. "</string>
    <string name="quarantine_10">✔\t Please contact your local or state health department as soon as possible in case of any emergency or irregularities in health</string>
    <string name="quarantine_9">✔\t Do not share dishes, drinking glasses, cups, eating utensils, towels or bedding with other people or pets in your home. After using these items, they should be washed thoroughly with soap and water.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_8">"✔\t Clean all high-touch surfaces daily which include counters, tabletops, doorknobs, bathroom fixtures, toilets, phones, keyboards, tablets, and bedside tables. "</string>
    <string name="quarantine_7">✔\t Avoid touching your eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_6">✔\t Wash your hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds or clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand sanitizer that contains 60 to 95% alcohol, covering all surfaces of your hands and rubbing them together until they feel dry.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_5">✔\t Cover your mouth and nose with a tissue when you cough or sneeze. Throw used tissues in a lined trash can.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_4">"✔\t Always wear a face mask when you are around other people (e.g., sharing a room or vehicle) or pets, and before you enter a health care provider’s office. "</string>
    <string name="quarantine_3">✔\t If you have a medical appointment, call the health care provider prior to your appointment and tell them that you have symptoms of COVID.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_2">✔\t Separate yourself from people and animals at home.</string>
    <string name="quarantine_1">✔\t Restrict activities outside your home, except for getting medical care. Under no circumstance you should go to work, school, or public areas. Avoid using public transportation, ride sharing, or taxis.</string>
    <string name="myth_1">Taking a hot bath DOES NOT prevent the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_2">Cold weather and snow CANNOT kill the CoronaVirus .</string>
    <string name="myth_4">There is NO evidence that companion animals/pets such as dogs or \t\tcats can transmit the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_3">The coronavirus CANNOT be transmitted through mosquito bites.</string>
    <string name="myth_5">Hand dryers are NOT effective in killing the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_6">Ultraviolet light SHOULD NOT be used for sterilization and can cause skin irritation.</string>
    <string name="myth_7">Spraying alcohol or chlorine all over your body WILL NOT kill viruses that have already entered your body.</string>
    <string name="myth_8">Antibiotics DO NOT work against viruses, antibiotics only work against bacteria.</string>
    <string name="myth_9">To date, there is NO specific medicine recommended to prevent or treat the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_10">Thermal scanners CAN detect if people have a fever but CANNOT detect whether or not someone has the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_11">Vaccines against pneumonia, such as pneumococcal vaccine and Haemophilus influenzae type b (Hib) vaccine, DO NOT provide \t\tprotection against the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_12">There is NO evidence that regularly rinsing the nose with saline has protected people from infection with the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_13">Garlic is healthy but there is NO evidence from the current outbreak that eating garlic has protected people from the coronavirus.</string>
    <string name="myth_14">The coronavirus CAN be transmitted in areas with hot and humid climates.</string>
    <string name="dos_1_head">LONG LASTING FRESH FUITS AND VEGETABLES</string>
    <string name="dos_1_body">✔\t WHO recommends consuming a minimum of 400g of fruits and vegetables per day such as citrus fruits,root vegetables etc</string>
    <string name="donts_1_head">LIMIT YOUR SALT INTAKE:</string>
    <string name="donts_1_body">✔\t WHO recommends consuming less than 5g of salt per day.</string>
    <string name="donts_3_head">LIMIT YOUR FAT INTAKE</string>
    <string name="donts_4_head">CONSUME ENOUGH FIBRE</string>
    <string name="donts_5_head">STAY HYDRATED</string>
    <string name="donts_6_head">AVOID ALCOHOLCONSUMPTION</string>
    <string name="donts_7_head">AVOID SMOKING</string>
    <string name="dos_3_head">FROZEN FRUITS AND VEGETABLES</string>
    <string name="dos_4_head">REDUCED-FAT,SHELF-STABLE MILK</string>
    <string name="dos_5_head">DRIED FRUITS, NUTS AND SEEDS</string>
    <string name="dos_6_head">EGGS</string>
    <string name="donts_2_body">✔\t WHO recommends that ideally less than 5% of total energy intake for adults</string>
    <string name="donts_3_body">✔\t WHO recommends limiting total fat intake to less than 30% of total energy intake,of which no more than 10% should come from the saturated fat.</string>
    <string name="donts_4_body">✔\t Fibre offers prolonged feeling of fullness,which prevents overeating.To ensure an adequate fibre intake,aim to include vegetables,fruits,wholegrain food like rice,oats,quinoa etc.</string>
    <string name="donts_5_body">✔\t Good hydration is crucial for optimal health.Avoid drinking large amount of strong coffee,strong tea and carbonated drinks.Try drinking hot/warm water and do not take cold water.</string>
    <string name="donts_6_body">✔\t Alcohol weakens immune system thus its heavy use undermines your body’s ability to cope with infectious disease,including COVID-19.It makes medications less effective,while increasing the potency and toxicity of others.Do not consume alcohol in combination with pain medication as it will interfere with liver function and might cause serious problems including liver failure.</string>
    <string name="donts_7_body">✔\t It makes the immune system of an individual weaker and increases the probability to become more prone to diseases.</string>
    <string name="dos_2_body">✔\t All frozen vegetables are great option as contain high level of fibre and vitamins.</string>
    <string name="dos_3_body">✔\t Beans,chickpeas,lentils and other pulses are great source of vegetable protein,fibre,vitamins and minerals.</string>
    <string name="dos_4_body">✔\t Dairy products provide an inexpensive source of protein and other nutrients.Choosing reduced-fat dairy is one way to reduce saturated fat consumption.UHT milk in a can or carton will be relatively shelf-stable.Powdered milk is another shelf-stable option.</string>
    <string name="dos_5_body">✔\t Particularly unsweetened and unsalted,these may serve as healthy snack or added to porridge,salads or other meals.</string>
    <string name="dos_6_body">✔\t They are a great source of protein and nutrients and are incredibly versatile.Opt for boiling or poached rather than frying.</string>
    <string name="dos">Do\'s</string>
    <string name="donts">Dont\'s</string>
    <string name="preventive_1">✔\t Regularly and thoroughly clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand rub or wash them with soap and water.</string>
    <string name="preventive_2">✔\t Avoid going to crowded places.</string>
    <string name="preventive_3">✔\t Avoid touching eyes, nose and mouth. .</string>
    <string name="preventive_4">✔\t Stay home and self-isolate even with minor symptoms such as cough, headache, mild fever, until you recover.</string>
    <string name="preventive_5">✔\t Cover your mouth and nose with a mask when around others.</string>
    <string name="preventive_6">✔\t Avoid unnecessary travelling.</string>
    <string name="preventive_7">✔\t Boost your immune system. Boosting your immune system can really help you here; with fresh food like veggies and fruits, involving oneself in indoor exercises, intake of essential nutrients like Vitamin B12 with Methylcobalamin, Magnesium etc.</string>
    <string name="preventive_8">✔\t To throw used tissues into closed bins immediately after use.</string>
    <string name="preventive_9">✔\t Use separate bedding and towels and not share these with other household members.</string>
    <string name="preventive_10">✔\t If water is not available,use hand sanitizer with atleast 60% alcohol.</string>
    <string name="health_1_head">1.\tEat a brain-healthy diet to support strong mental health</string>
    <string name="health_1_body">An unhealthy diet can take a toll on your brain and mood, disrupt your sleep, sap your energy, and weaken your immune system. Conversely, switching to a wholesome diet, low in sugar and rich in healthy fats, can give you more energy, improve your sleep and mood.</string>
    <string name="health_sub_1">Foods that adversely affect mood</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_1">✔\t Caffeine</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_2">✔\t Alcohol</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_3">✔\t Trans fats or anything with “partially hydrogenated” oil</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_4">✔\t Foods with high levels of chemical preservatives or hormones</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_5">✔\t Sugary snacks</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_6">✔\t Refined carbs such as white rice or white flour</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_7">✔\t Fried food</string>
    <string name="health_sub_2">Foods that boost mood</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_8">✔\t Fatty fish rich in Omega-3s such as salmon, herring, mackerel, anchovies, sardines, tuna</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_9">✔\t Nuts such as walnuts, almonds, cashews, peanuts</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_10">✔\t Avocados</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_11">✔\t Flaxseed</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_12">✔\t Beans</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_13">✔\t Leafy greens such as spinach, kale, Brussel’s sprouts</string>
    <string name="health_bullet_14">✔\t Fresh fruit such as blueberries</string>
    <string name="health_2_head">2.Manage emotions to relieve stress:</string>
    <string name="health_2_body">"✔\t Understanding and accepting your emotions—especially those unpleasant ones many of us try to ignore—can make a huge difference in your ability to manage stress and balance your moods. "</string>
    <string name="health_3_head">3.Talk about your feelings:</string>
    <string name="health_3_body">✔\t Talking about your feelings can help you stay in good mental health and deal with times when you feel troubled.</string>
    <string name="health_4_head">4.Drink sensibly:</string>
    <string name="health_4_body">✔\t We often drink alcohol to change our mood. Some people drink to deal with fear or loneliness, but the effect is only temporary.When the drink wears off, you feel worse. Drinking is not a good way to manage difficult feelings.</string>
    <string name="health_5_head">5.Do something you’re good at:</string>
    <string name="health_5_body">✔\t What do you love doing? What activities can you lose yourself in? What did you love doing in the past? Enjoying yourself can help beat stress </string>
    <string name="health_6_head">6.Accept who you are:</string>
    <string name="health_6_body">✔\t We’re all different. It’s much healthier to accept that you’re unique than to wish you were more like someone else. Feeling good about yourself boosts your confidence.</string>
    <string name="health_7_head">7. Ask for help:</string>
    <string name="health_7_body">✔\t No one is a superhuman. We all sometimes get tired or overwhelmed by how we feel or when things don’t go to plan. If things are getting too much for you and you feel you can’t cope, ask for help from your family or friends.</string>
    <string name="diet_plan_note">"Note:- Our recommended diet plan is  exclusively  designed on the basis of your answers asked  during the self-assessment Test. If you allergic to  any of the food items please do not intake them.  "</string>
    <string name="diet_plan_diagnose_text">"Based on the test we found out that you have a condition of  "</string>
    <string name="diet_plan_recommend">"We would recommend you to enjoy your meals to the fullest but exclude the  enlisted foods in the next page from your diet "</string>
    <string name="diet_plan_avoid">"AVOID including the following in your  meals: "</string>
    <string name="disease">Do you have a history of any of these diseases?</string>
    <string name="unique_result">Due to some technical errors the result for your test could not be  shown, please try again l  ater. WE APOLOGIZE FOR THE  INCONVINIENC</string>
    <string name="feedback">, thank you for using our app! Help us serve you better , do share your valuable feedback by clicking on the button below. We would really like to hear your experience using this app and would appreciate your suggestions that would help us improve the User Experience.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>